A snapshot of T.B. Joshua's ministry
The man T.B. Joshua
Prophet T.B. Joshua is the founder and general overseer of The Synagogue, Church of All Nations,
an international Christian ministry established 27 years ago.
He is also the principle coordinator of Emmanuel TV,
the universally renowned media house dedicated to changing lives, reconciling families
and transforming nations through the Spirit of God.
Amen!
I don't know where to start.
My coming into your midst is just to lay a foundation.
Today, we start The Synagogue here!
The ministry began in a humble way, from Prophet T.B. Joshua starting with just eight members.
Today, the church has grown beyond the confines of any country or continent -
transcending language and cultural barriers with a message of hope and healing, freedom and deliverance -
displayed through the mighty miracles at The Synagogue, Church of All Nations.
Emmanuel TV has become the most watched Christian channel in the whole continent of Africa.
It has taken YouTube by storm with hundreds of millions of views
and hundreds of thousands of subscribers.
Every day, hundreds of sick and afflicted people cry out for the attention of our Lord Jesus.
As it was so it is today - Jesus Christ healed and still heals all manner of sicknesses and diseases.
This festering hand is condemned to amputation.
Prophet T.B. Joshua prays in the power of the Holy Spirit,
and she is healed in Jesus' name.
This is her testimony for the glory of God.
I am healed!
There is nothing that I cannot use this hand to do!
I wash clothes, I cook; I do everything with this hand.
Another shocking case is Mr. Hennie Ferreira from South Africa who came to The Synagogue, Church of All Nations
with gaping bones caused by cancer that had spread to both legs.
The incurable leg cancer that had defied the best medical treatments
succumbed to the power in the name of Jesus Christ.
As Prophet T.B. Joshua offers prayers of faith, watch as healing takes place.
This is the leg. You can see I have got no pain anymore.
My leg is completely healed.
Thank God for that!
Before and After
Young Nosa came to The Synagogue, Church of All Nations with eye cancer.
His eye which bore the brunt of his affliction
soon became the trophy of Christ's victory in his life,
after prayer from Prophet T.B. Joshua in the name of Jesus Christ.
Before and After
Sent to the nations, Prophet T.B. Joshua takes the gospel of Jesus Christ to the four corners of the earth.
Botswana 2005
The country of Botswana, located in the Southern African region,
was the first nation where Prophet T.B. Joshua held a crusade.
People jumped and cheered with excitement and hearts full of faith
as Prophet T.B. Joshua arrived for the historical visit.
I am here to do what I am born for, and I am living for, and I am going to die for.
On the crusade ground, crutches and wheelchairs were raised high
as people regained their ability to walk.
The stands were filled to capacity.
Botswana Crusade 2005
If millions of this generation are to believe, they must see the evidence
that Jesus Christ is the same yesterday, today and forever.
Never a healer like Jesus Christ.
Jesus Christ is the permanent solution who changes not.
Who else can justly heal - it's none other than Jesus Christ.
What a son we have to worship, what a God we have to praise.
Glory be to God!
Botswana Crusade 2005
I don't need to use these things anymore.
I am a free woman.
Hallelujah!
The Korea for Christ Crusade with Prophet T.B. Joshua.
This is the evidence that there is healing in the name of Jesus Christ.
Thousands witnessed the power in the name of Jesus.
Indeed, when the power of God is present, freedom, deliverance is just like breathing.
The Royal Opera House in Sydney, Australia, marks another crusade destination
where Prophet T.B. Joshua was sent, bringing practical Christianity to the four corners of the earth.
At the Australia for Christ Crusade with Prophet T.B. Joshua.
God used his servant and those who were sick and bound, were healed and set free.
Chains holding people in bondage were broken in the name of Jesus Christ.
Come out!
Out!
Australia Crusade 2006
Come out!
I had a demon which has been true for fifteen years.
God has delivered me from it.
Thank You, Jesus.
Singapore Crusade 2006
Hundreds of thousands also gathered at the Singapore Crusade with T.B. Joshua
where God demonstrated His mighty power to heal, deliver and set the captives free.
Prophet T.B. Joshua prays for this woman, proving that the right hand of God is power indeed.
Singapore Crusade 2006
Thank You, my Jesus! Thank You!
Walking appreciatively after her healing, she not only thanks Jesus,
but His servant who was used to perform the miracle in His name.
God really wants to heal, but unless you believe, you will not experience it.
It's tremendous and this is the first time I have seen
where deliverance is being done on a massive scale.
I think he is very anointed to demonstrate the power from God
so that the people will understand Jesus.
I am from Indonesia.
I saw a lot of miracles happening here; it's really amazing.
To me, I was thinking all this is just magic - I have to be very open -
and today I really got the privilege and got blessed
and I accept Jesus as the Saviour of my life.
Please clap for Jesus Christ.
It is time for healing.
Prophet T.B. Joshua in Singapore
Be healed, in Jesus' name!
You are healed. Walk - you are healed.
National Healing Campaign in Singapore with Prophet T.B. Joshua
You are healed. Stand up!
Those of you that have no faith, I will pray for you -
your faith will be enough.
Stand up!
Begin to stand up!
Prophet T.B. Joshua in Singapore
Prophet T.B. Joshua delivers God's message of hope, faith and love
to an arena of people, hungry for the power of God in the nation of Indonesia.
Indonesia Crusade - Prophet T.B. Joshua
Hallelujah!
Thanks, Jesus!
This is the Pascual Guerrero Olympic Stadium in Cali, Colombia
where thousands of people from across Latin America and around the world
streamed in for just a touch from Heaven
through His anointed servant Prophet T.B. Joshua.
The stadium is filled to capacity, as they await a touch
that will change the course of the history of their lives forever.
Come out, in the name of Jesus Christ!
There is never a sickness Jesus cannot heal, never a disease Jesus cannot cure,
never a problem Jesus cannot solve.
I feel free.
I can move freely without the lumbar corset I used to use.
I arrived at home from the stadium by 12am when everyone was sleeping.
I was full of Christ and anointing like I had just returned from a celebration!
I took my corset in my hand, threw it on the floor and stamped on it!
Colombia Pastors' Conference with Prophet T.B. Joshua - Testimony Time
Thank You for remembering Colombia!
Pastor Edgar Castano - Bautista Central, Bogota, Colombia
I am the president of CEDECOL, the Evangelical Federation of Colombia,
which comprises the majority of the churches in the country.
He said that his name is Edgar Castano and he is from Bogota
and he is the president of CEDECOL which is the majority of all the Colombian churches -
a network of all the churches in Colombia.
It was impressive to see the huge crowd that came to the event.
I was especially impressed to see the deliverances and the miracles.
I strongly believe in the relationship between the Word and miracles,
that is, between theology and miracles.
I believe that the Word of God has power to bring miracles.
In my opinion, it was a great blessing for me to be here.
He said, it was very powerful to see the miracles and the Word of God, that the two should work together.
T.B. Joshua travelled to Mexico, home of the Aztec Stadium,
where thousands rushed to experience God's power and celebrate the Prince of peace
with songs of praise from renowned musicians like Alvin Slaughter,
Cece Winans and VaShawn Mitchell.
The people praised God as they saw Prophet T.B. Joshua being used as the instrument in His hands
to make the lame walk, deaf to hear and the blind to see.
Mexico Crusade 2015
I cannot see - for sixteen years.
After stating her case of being blind for sixteen years,
Prophet T.B. Joshua prays for her and she falls under the mighty anointing of God,
causing blindness to bow and flee at the mention of the name Jesus Christ.
Mexico Crusade 2015
I am free!
Hallelujah!
I can see!
Mexico Crusade 2015
For two and a half years he cannot walk.
The femur on the left leg is dead, the cartilage is dead.
He is ten years old.
Watch as Prophet T.B. Joshua prays for this young boy in the power of the Holy Ghost.
Mexico Crusade 2015
A clear proof that he no longer needs the crutches
and can now walk freely after Prophet T.B. Joshua prayed for him.
Glory be to God.
Mexico Crusade 2015
Help me, Man of God. I cannot move my neck
I have a stiff neck.
As directed by the Holy Spirit, Prophet T.B. Joshua prays for this woman
wearing a neck collar due to a stiff neck at the prayer line of the Mexico Crusade.
Watch a spiritual operation as it takes place.
Jesus has done it again.
Who could question so much evidence that Jesus lives. He never said goodbye.
Mexico Crusade 2015
Thank You, Jesus! I am free!
After her healing turning her neck from side to side, up and down, fully restored,
no one would guess that she was the same young woman who was once wincing in pain
and subject to a neck collar only hours before.
Glory be to God!
The Sky Dome in Seoul, South Korea,
was the venue of the 2016 South Korea Crusade with Prophet T.B. Joshua -
his third appearance in the country.
Heart and souls were lifted as those in attendance praised the name of the Most High God.
As the book of Psalms 22:3 says:
"He inhabits the praises of His people."
They render songs of worship while waiting expectantly for His much loved servant.
Thank you.
South Korea Crusade 2016
I want to be healed, in Jesus' name.
As this woman prays in faith for her healing to come, Prophet T.B. Joshua is used as a point of contact
for the lightning power of God to become apparent on the scene.
Surely within moments of contact, healing takes place instantaneously.
South Korea Crusade 2016
I want to tell you guys that you shouldn't have doubt.
As we count our many blessings, doubt will flee.
This is just one of many cases showing just how great our God is.
Here is another - a young man whose mobility and movement is hindered by his affliction.
South Korea Crusade 2016
I wasn't able to do pushups because of the pains in my wrist and shoulders.
At the name of Jesus Christ, he is free.
No longer bound by the pain in his wrist and shoulders,
he is not only able to do pushups, but exercise every part of his body.
The Synagogue, Church of All Nations started from the giving ministry.
Right from the beginning of this ministry, it has been a church and giving ministry.
What comes from the church goes to the ministry of giving to raise the standard of living.
Help the needy, help the widow, help the orphan.
Nigeria - Physically Challenged Outreach
Emmanuel TV - Philippines Typhoon Relief Team
Everything is gone - our houses, everything. There is nothing to eat, there is nothing to drink.
Do you have water or food there?
Here are members of the Emmanuel TV Team in the Phillipines giving to the needy victims affected by the storm.
Emmanuel TV - Haiti Earthquake Relief
Haiti - Earthquake Disaster Relief
Emmanuel TV - Disaster Relief
Ecuador - Earthquake Disaster Relief
My People FC
My People FC - Youth Empowerment
Colombia - Reaching Families in Need
USA, Colorado - Homeless Outreach
USA, Ohio - Homeless Outreach
USA - Elderly Outreach
Pakistan - Establishing Emmanuel School
Thank you for the school!
T.B. Joshua, through his ministry and Emmanuel TV, has touched so many lives across the world
through humanitarian and philanthropic deeds,
including providing academic scholarships for many beneficiaries such as children and young adults.
These scholarships have enabled them to reach the heights of their academic dreams
that would have otherwise crashed on the rocks of poverty.
Beneficiaries such as Miss Olayinka Oduwole, sponsored to the University College of London
and later Oxford University where she is undergoing her PhD course.
To Emmanuel TV Partners: Thank you for everything you have done.
This wouldn't have been possible without you.
And most importantly: Thank you, Prophet T.B. Joshua.
Miss Mary Jean Nleya sponsored to Harvard University for her Masters degree programme
and later internship at the ICC (International Criminal Court) in the Hague.
My time here at Harvard has been amazing.
I have been taught by renowned professors. I have dedicated my Masters thesis to Prophet T.B. Joshua
and by the grace of God my Masters thesis was graded with honours by my professor
who was incredibly impressed with the work that I had done through this thesis.
Many people see T.B. Joshua's ministry, The Synagogue, Church of All Nations, in Nigeria as a place of refuge.
This stranded lady from Mongolia came with her two children in dire need of passports
and airfare to return to their country.
This is my passport. The man of God helped me to get my passport.
Thank You, Jesus!, Thank You, God! Thank you, Man of God!
Thank you, Nigeria.
T.B. Joshua and the Emmanuel.TV Partners provided them with their complete travel expenses
and worked with the Mongolian embassy in Egypt to acquire the passports of her two children.
Tears of desperation fall down the cheeks of this woman from Indonesia.
She and her family also found help at The Synagogue, Church of All Nations
after they found themselves in extreme poverty.
Prophet T.B. Joshua wants to assure you, sir, that he is going to help you to find a job.
Secondly, he said that he is here today to give you the sum of 500,000 Naira
and for our sister here from Indonesia who has stated publicly that she is requesting help
from the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua, to return to Indonesia with her children,
the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua, said the ministry here, The Synagogue, Church of All Nations
and Emmanuel TV Partners are going to take up your travelling back to Indonesia with our two children.
The ministry will take care of getting all of your travel documents, getting your passports -
every document you need - your flight tickets to the sum of 7,000 USD
for you and your two children.
Aside from all of the costs that it will take to transport you back to Indonesia,
Prophet T.B. Joshua and Emmanuel TV Partners are additionally giving you the sum of 3,000 USD
so that you can start a new life afresh in Indonesia with your children.
And your two children will be given scholarships to their various educational levels back in Indonesia.
So once again, brethren, this is the message from our father in the Lord, Prophet T.B. Joshua,
for himself and Emmanuel TV Partners worldwide who have heard this case.
As we said, as Christians we cannot afford to look the other way when we see our neighbours in trouble.
Our sister came in tears to The Synagouge, Church of All Nations on the streets with her little chrilden
and today to the glory of God, the mission of Emmanuel TV - you can see it in the lives of this family -
changing lives, changing nations and changing the world!
T.B. Joshua's philanthropic deeds have also reached the shores of the Holy land of Israel!
This is T.B. Joshua and ZAKA Chairman, Rabbi Yehuda Meshi Zahav,
as he honours him with an award for his humanitarian work.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Prays With Rabbi Yehuda At ZAKA's New Site In Israel
I am Roberts Liardon, a pastor from America and the Author of the "God's Generals" series.
I hope you have spent a part of your day,
every day listening to the great messages and the great spirit that comes from this network.
It will change your life.
My name is Bill Subritzky and I am from New Zealand -
a small country, 12 hundred miles from Australia.
This is Kaylin, my wife - a woman of God.
The Holy Spirit always kept saying: "This is a man of God, support him".
And I thank God for Prophet Joshua.
This is Evangelist C.S. Upthegrove
and my biggest advice to you is to keep watching Emmanuel TV.
God will bless you for that! Amen!
I knew William Branham, Jack Coe, I knew Oral Roberts.
I knew these men, I go all the way back to the healing days
and I knew all of the signs and wonders - I have been in their services. Now I rejoice.
I have been with Kathryn Kuhlman. I have seen so many.
But listen! Everything that I'm seeing in the ministry right now of Prophet Joshua
supersedes anthing that I have seen under those ministries.
It is a greater measure and it is exactly what brother Allen said would happen.
God used this stamp in the hands of A.A. Allen. So it is my pleasure to present to you this stamp.
This is the signature stamp of A.A. Allen given to C.S. Upthegrove by the late God's General
and handed over to another God's General, Prophet T.B. Joshua.